The World Pipe Band Championships will take place in Glasgow on Saturday.
Over 120 of the world's best pipe bands will compete at the Championships.
Over 120 of the world's best pipe bands will compete at
Over 4,000 pipers and drummers are expected to descend on the city for the annual
event. Over 4,000 pipers and drummers are expected to descend on the city for the
annual event. Over 4,000 pipers and drummers are expected to descend on the city for
the annual event.
It will take place at the St.
James Playing Fields in Glasgow on Saturday, 18 May from 10 am until 7 pm.
The event is free.
Also, a free shuttle bus will run between the event car parks and the competition
site. The event is free.
site. Shuttle buses will run every 15 minutes from 8 am until 8 pm.
Glasgow City Council says it is estimated to bring 300,000 pounds to the local
economy. Shuttle buses will run every 15 minutes from 8 am until 8 pm.
economy. The first World Pipe Band Championships were held in Edinburgh in 1947.
The event first took place in Glasgow in